Yanni Haddad, Undergraduate Student

P: 0490664504, E: yannihaddad@gmail.com

PROFILE

Highly capable individual with great interpersonal and problem-solving skills with extensive experience in analytical/people-centric roles. I'm a fast learner with an eye for detail and will fit right into any organisation with a great team dynamic.

EDUCATION

Jul 2021 — Present

Bachelor of Computer Science & Economics, UNSW

(Distinction WAM)

Extra-curricular activities: UNSW YALA treasurer, AIAA Competition Team Member, CSESoc Projects Team Member, UNSW Anjali Oztag Coordinator, UNSW BSOC Peer Mentoring, CSESOC Peer Mentoring

Jan 2015 — Sep 2020

Greystanes High School

(98.15 ATAR)

Highlights: School DUX, School Captain

Leadership: House captain, SRC, Peer Support Leader, Exchange student ambassador, EDUTECH Coordinator/presenter, Young Creator's conference coordinator/presenter, ESL support program, Peer tutoring program facilitator (yr 7-12), Volunteering committee.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Oct 2021 — Present

NRL Data Analyst, StatPerform

Sydney

- Utilised data software to analyse and code the offensive/defensive stats of NRL, NRLW, NSW Cup, HotPlus Cup (QLD) and Super League matches in real time.
- Worked diligently in a team of 8 coders to ensure final output is meticulously constructed and sent out to our contractors within 2 hours of full-time.
- Collaborated with other coders on projects to alleviate any inquiries or issues that the broadcasters (Channel 9), betting agencies, fantasy football leagues and/or the NRL coaching units may come across.

Nov 2021 — Feb 2022

UI/UX Designer Intern, Core Intelligence INC

- Enhanced skills in UX/UI design and expertise with Figma creating low/high fidelity wireframes for a contracted start-up JobLaunch
- Gained proficiency in python/JavaScript, HTML, CSS and Web Developer Tools.
- Published a Bootcamp article in Don Norman's 'The Design of Everyday Things' which bolstered my
 understanding of design in the context of digital products.

Jul 2021 — Nov 2021

Membership Representative (Sales), Freedom Property Investors

Sydney

- Coordinated Masterclasses with a team of property consultants, specialists and membership representatives to manage client inquires and overall logistics.
- Independently closed sales and Maintained weekly KPIs, e.g 900 dials, +30 rebooks, +8hrs call time.
- Placed a huge emphasis on membership experience and genuinely showed interest & amp; care towards
 helping clients solve their financial problems, through investing in residential property.
- Further developed my verbal & written communication skills by learning to become a more empathetic listener and compelling speaker.

Oct 2021 — Mar 2022

HP Brand Ambassador (Sales / JB-HI-FI), D2C Consumers

Sydney

- Engaged with customers in store, promoting the key features of, and selling technological appliances on behalf of HP (consistently maintained KPIs).
- Tailored sales approaches and techniques to specific client needs to increase market effectiveness.
- Boosted Brand awareness, implemented promotional campaigns and employed sales tactics as part of territory development.
- Built meaningful and constructive relationships with store staff to help maximize sales.

LEADERSHIP

Feb 2022 — Present

Treasurer, UNSW YALA

· Managing, Budgeting and Accounting for finances of Society

Nov 2021 — Present	Projects Team Member, UNSW CSESoc
	2021-2022 – CSESoc projects team member
Oct 2019 — Oct 2020	School Captain, Greystanes High School
	2018-2020 – Peer Mentor
	2018-2019 – SRC Treasurer
	2017-2018 – House Captain
	2016-2019 – SRC Representative
Jan 2020 — Nov 2020	CHS Open Boys Soccer Captain
	2019-2020 – Open boys oztag (vice captain)
	2016-2020 – Rugby 9's KO Competition
	2015-2020 – Knockout boys Soccer, Cricket, Oztag Team
AWARDS	
2017 — 2020	School DUX
2020	Blacktown Zone Leadership Award
2019	Young Creator's Conference Best Presenter

References available upon request

REFERENCES